

ABOUT ME

I reconverted my professional career as a full-stack web developer. Spent the last 5 years studying Economics and working in the financial industry, first as a data analyst and then developing machine learning models to help reduce loan and credit card debt defaults.

CONTACT INFORMATION

PHONE: +5491127536400

EMAIL: begonzalez1993@gmail.com https://github.com/bernigonzalez

https://www.linkedin.com/in/bernardo-gonzalez-/

LOCATION: Argentina / Remote

EDUCATION

Henry Bootcamp

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

dEC 2021 - APR 2022

Javascript inmersive Bootcamp.

+700 hours of coding in 4 months

UNIVERSIDAD UADE

BS ECONOMICS

2014 - 2020 IN PAUSE, 70% OF THE PATH COMPLETED

BERNARDO GONZALEZ

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

JAVASCRIPT | REACT | REDUX | NODE

WORK EXPERIENCE

RISK MODEL ANALYST

FALABELLA FINANCIERO, MAR 2019 - JAN 2022

Development and monitoring of machine learning models to reduce loan/credit cards debt defaults and to increase debt collections

RISK DATA ANALYST

FALABELLA FINANCIERO, FEB 2018 - MAR 2019

Aggregate and compile business data based on requests from senior leadership with a focus on risk assessment, credit quality , market segment opportunities and business development.

RISK DATA ANALYST

SUPERVIELLE BANK, SEP 2017 - FEB 2018

- Write queries or reports to provide data for various analytical projects.
- Integrate data from multiple data sources, ensure data accuracy, and update data as needed.

CO-FOUNDER

FOOD SAFARI, SEP 2016 - DEC 2017

Startup that offered "surprise" dining experiences in which the customer did not know the destination until they arrived at the location. It included a round trip in Cabify and dinner at some of the top restaurants in Buenos Aires.

https://www.instagram.com/foodsafariok/

INTERNSHIP

HSBC BANK, MAR 2016 - SEP 2017